fitmob.com 2019-04-10

# ClassPass | Privacy Policy

The ClassPass website and mobile applications (the “Site”) are operated by ClassPass Inc. ClassPass is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. To that end, we have prepared this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to describe our information gathering and dissemination practices and our data protection practices for the Site. Please read this policy carefully so that you understand our privacy practices. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, do not use the Site or give us any of your information. The terms “ClassPass,” “we,” “us,” and “our” refer to ClassPass Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliates. The terms “you,” “your,” and “yours” refer to the user/customer utilizing the Site. This Privacy Policy is governed by our Terms of Use. 

## COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

“Personally Identifiable Information” means any information which can be used to identify an individual, and may include, but is not limited to, name, email address, or postal or other physical address. We collect Personally Identifiable Information from you when you register for the Site, including the following: name and email address. To participate in certain activities and to obtain certain services or documents offered on the Site, you may be asked to provide additional Personally Identifiable Information such as phone number, billing address and credit card information. We endeavor to limit our requests for Personally Identifiable Information to information we believe is reasonably necessary to achieve our purposes as described in the “Information Use” section below. Any Personally Identifiable Information received in communication or in material you transmit to the Site by electronic mail or otherwise are and will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy. When you visit the Site we also collect non-personally identifiable information, which is information that by itself cannot be used to identify or contact you, such as demographic information (such as age or gender) or usage information (such as the browser you are using, the URL that referred you to the Site and the areas of the Site you visit). We may also supplement the information we collect with information from other sources to assist us in evaluating and improving our Site and offerings.

## INFORMATION USE

ClassPass uses Personally Identifiable Information for several general purposes:

  * to provide you with the Site, service information, and news,
  * to support the Site and services offered on or through the Site,
  * to contact you for feedback about our services,
  * to conduct research about ClassPass’s customer base or services,
  * to fulfill your reservation and purchase requests,
  * to process your payments including credit checks and collection,
  * to notify you of technical updates or changes in policy, or
  * to contact you for our own marketing and promotional purposes, or
  * to process contests, sweepstakes, or other promotions and fulfill any related awards or discounts.

We may use non-Personally Identifiable Information such as demographic data to analyze and develop our marketing strategy and further improve the Site and our services.

## INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

We will not sell or rent your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties except as described in this Privacy Policy. We may disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to other companies or people under any of the following circumstances:

  * to any applicable venue, studio, instructor, or other service provider for each class or activity that you sign up for on the Site and their third-party providers, so they can process the applicable reservation, make available services to you and contact you regarding the activity you reserved and send you other communication that may be of interest say as special offers (you may opt-out of marketing communications directly with the applicable venue).
  * if sharing the information is reasonably necessary to provide or otherwise make available the Site and any feature of the Site or a service.
  * to keep you up to date on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, or other information we think you would like to hear about either from us or from our business partners (unless you have opted out of these types of communications). (Note that you will not be able to opt-out of service announcements that contain important information relevant to your use of the Site and are not promotional in nature.)
  * to other users of our Site to enable them to connect with you. When you create an account on the Site, you will automatically be able to participate in certain social features which allow you to connect with other ClassPass accountholders. Other ClassPass accountholders will be able to find you by your name and will be able to see certain information about you, such as your name, city, and profile photo. You can always choose in your Privacy Settings (in the app) whether or not to turn off being findable and you can also choose to turn off certain information your friends see about you, such as your upcoming classes, class history, and favorite studios.
  * ClassPass may allow you to access to a variety of audio or video digital classes from your computer or mobile device, via live stream and/or on demand. When you participate in these digital classes through a connected device, such as a heartrate monitor, we may collect heartrate and other metrics to calculate your ranking in the leaderboard, display a record of your participation and otherwise provide, learn about and improve the Site and our services. If you sync your heart rate monitor with the Site to participate in digital classes, you will automatically be part of the leaderboard experience, and other participants in the class will see your profile information (including your profile picture and username) and rank in the class. In addition, we may display this information or your rank on our Site, for example to display that you were a top participant that week. If you do not want your profile information to be seen by other ClassPass users, do not include any identifying information.
  * if we believe in good faith that we are required to do so by law, in connection with litigation, to prevent a crime, or to protect personal property, the public, or the Site.
  * in connection with a sale or merger with another entity, consolidation, restructuring, sale of company assets, financing or other corporate change, including during the course of any due diligence process or if ClassPass should ever file for bankruptcy or related proceeding.
  * to your employer (or similar entity), if you participate in any of enterprise solutions or corporate programs.
  * when we otherwise have your consent to share the information.

ClassPass may also share non-Personally Identifiable Information with third parties (e.g. aggregate or demographic data).

## CHOICE

We will give you the opportunity to “opt out” of receiving direct marketing or market research information. This means we assume you have given us your consent to collect and use your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy unless you take affirmative action to indicate that you do not consent, for instance by opting out through the mechanism provided in the emails we send.

## ACCESS

You may correct, amend, or update your Personally Identifiable Information by editing your profile on the Site or contacting us.

## SECURITY

We are committed to protecting Personally Identifiable Information from loss, misuse, disclosure, alteration, unauthorized access, and destruction. ClassPass takes reasonable precautions to safeguard the confidentiality of Personally Identifiable Information. We protect the security of your Personally Identifiable Information during transmission to us by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the information you input.

## THIRD PARTY SITES

The Site may contain links to other sites. ClassPass is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when leaving the Site to read the privacy statements of each site that collects Personally Identifiable Information.

### COOKIES

We use cookies and other similar technologies (such as actions tags, also known as beacons, or pixels tags) for a number of purposes including to remember preferences, track conversions, conduct marketing and promotional efforts, analyze site traffic and trends, and generally understand the online behaviors and interests of people who interact with our Site.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements on our behalf or to provide advertising-related services. These companies may use a cookie or an action tag, to tailor the advertisements you see on this Website and other sites, to track your response to their advertisement, to determine whether advertising has been served and to measure the effectiveness of their advertising or to award incentives or points to their members who respond to their advertisements. The cookies, action tags or similar files do not contain any Personal Information.

You can learn more about targeted advertising, its benefits and your choices by going to the Digital Advertising Alliance site at <http://www.aboutads.info/consumers/>. The targeted advertising companies we work with are members of the Network Advertising Initiative or the DAA. The NAI and the DAA allow you to limit targeted advertising from its members by using an opt-out tool available on the NAI website at [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp) or the DAA’s site.

We may also use third parties to provide measurement and analytic services. You can find more information on Google Analytics by visiting <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

## SOCIAL MEDIA FEATURES AND WIDGETS

Our Site may integrate with social sharing features or other related tools which let you share actions you take on our Site with other apps, sites or media, and vice versa. These features may enable the sharing of information with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the social sharing service. These features may also collect your IP address and which page you are visiting on our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Your interaction with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the relevant platform. Please refer to the privacy policies of those social sharing services for more information.

## PUBLIC POSTS

The Site may allow you to post or share content to a public area of the Site such as a public profile, group, community or other public area. You should be aware that any content or information you choose to disclose in these areas can be read, collected and used by other users, the general public and other sites (including search engines). We are not responsible for, and this Privacy Policy does not apply to, information you may choose to post in these areas.

## YOUR CONSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

By using this Site, you agree to this Privacy Policy. We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. The date of the most recent update of this document will always be displayed at the beginning of this page. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on classpass.com. If we decide to use Personally Identifiable Information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users via email (if an email address has been provided) or display a notice on classpass.com. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we are protecting the Personally Identifiable Information we collect. Your continued use of this Site constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.

## CONTACTING CLASSPASS

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

ClassPass Inc.  
P.O. Box 20196  
Greeley Sq Station  
New York, NY 10001

Or contact us here.

**Last updated:** July 9, 2018
